Gary Young: Hello, Mr. Wade.
Wade: Mr. Wade was my father, just call me Wade.
Gary Young: Alright.
Gary Young: My wife's last name is Lee, so I actually like going by Mr. Lee sometimes.
Gary Young: Preferably with the accent, Mr. Lee.
Wade: My last name is, Brown, and my neighbor's last name is White, and boy, is he tickled by that.
Wade: Like, he came to deliver some mail, and he's like, I didn't know you were white and I'm brown, or you were brown and I'm white?
Wade: Okay, he's like a 75-year-old, he's a super nice guy.
David Mendenhall: Let me call Custatis. I predict Costatas forgot.
Wade: I don't know, he linked the message to me saying that this was happening, so…
David Mendenhall: No, that was me. I did that.
Wade: Oh, alright.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I'm gonna call him.
Gary Young: Well, Dave linked the copy of Quesada's.
Wade: Oh, yeah, I see it now. David Mendenhall quoted Costada.
David Mendenhall: Forwarded to voicemail, not a good sign. He turned his phone off.
Gary Young: Okay.
Gary Young: Is he traveling or something?
David Mendenhall: No, he's back.
Gary Young: We're back.
Wade: He has no excuse not to love us.
David Mendenhall: I could try Natasha.
David Mendenhall: She'll be really annoyed if I call her.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Wade: I don't think she likes us.
David Mendenhall: out.
Gary Young: It's only 9PM.
Wade: My only experience with her.
David Mendenhall: I could get Amy to call her.
David Mendenhall: She likes Amy more than me.
Wade: Oh, oh, look, there he is!
David Mendenhall: Here I was debating whether to call Natasha or not. I don't have to do it.
Kostadis Roussos: Send a note to Stefan.
David Mendenhall: Hey, man.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, man, how are you?
David Mendenhall: Weren't sure if you're gonna make it.
Kostadis Roussos: I was gonna make it. Me not make it? Come on, man.
Kostadis Roussos: Of course I was gonna make it.
David Mendenhall: If you remember, it's hard to remember sometimes.
Wade: I forget, I mean, this is off, off schedule.
David Mendenhall: Is it, yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And it is pretty early for me, too.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Stefan, you joined?
David Mendenhall: Come on,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, I'm here.
David Mendenhall: Rejoining from Stefan.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: France.
David Mendenhall: Oh…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It is 6 AM today.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I've done the 6 AM game several times.
Kostadis Roussos: He's, like, he's showing real commitment, because he lives in France, right?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, absolutely.
Wade: Oh, dear.
Wade: There's no pressure for us to get a good session, then, huh?
Gary Young: Next week, I'm in, Manhattan, so, this slot will be midnight.
David Mendenhall: Next week, I'm out.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: in here.
David Mendenhall: So… well, Tuesday, I'm on an airplane, so…
Kostadis Roussos: I, I… well, we should find a way to… okay, let's, let's, so let's…
Gary Young: I would be back Friday night, though.
David Mendenhall: play.
Wade: Alright, let's play. Let's play.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: We're all here.
Wade: I load up my character sheets and such, but…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Wade: I remember…
Kostadis Roussos: I provided appropriate summaries.
Wade: I missed a dragon attack? What the hell?
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, what you missed was… it was something far more spectacular.
David Mendenhall: It's me!
David Mendenhall: Single-handedly defeating a dragon, spell!
Wade: I saw that! I saw that the bard got, you know, bardic behavior for once.
David Mendenhall: Great.
Gary Young: And I negotiated enemy of my enemy as my friend.
Wade: Yeah, that…
Gary Young: temporary out.
David Mendenhall: That was not… yeah, that was…
Wade: Was it… that hit different.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to get something to drink, hold on, hold on.
Wade: We forced.
David Mendenhall: And then what we're…
David Mendenhall: Well, what he didn't write about was how you then lied about it to all of us, but I guess we're changing that?
Gary Young: Yeah, I was hoping that she would just not realize that that was a problem.
Wade: By the way…
David Mendenhall: I've signed up a new ally!
Wade: JK, JK!
Gary Young: Temporarily!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Our enemy.
Wade: Well, we have our enemies.
David Mendenhall: Mr. Ruse.
Wade: Hey, hey.
Wade: So… You're tits.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, so let me just make sure I remember what happened.
Wade: Yeah, it's important the GM knows.
Gary Young: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Stefan, where do you live in France?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I live in a city called Clermont Ferrants. That's right smack in the middle of France, in the middle of nowhere.
David Mendenhall: middle of nowhere.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's a rural area. It's where the old volcanoes are.
Gary Young: Oh.
David Mendenhall: No.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: very fertile plains, and I mean, the only, I guess we're famous for a few things, one is the rugby team. We got a good rugby team.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Two is, we've got a black cathedral, because it's made out of, volcanic stone.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And, 3 is, we've got the Michelin headquarters.
David Mendenhall: Is it, like, between, like, Orlean and Lyon?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, sort of, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Sort of, okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Between Orleans and Lyon would be, like, sort of a diagonal, I guess.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: From north… somewhere up north to the east.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And Claremont Ferrant would be south of, Orleans.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And west of you.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: She's at Claremont Faron?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Cremont Ferrant, yeah?
David Mendenhall: Oh, I see it on the map now, I see it. It's not that small, it's on the map.
Gary Young: It's a pretty cool looking cathedral.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Thank you.
David Mendenhall: Lomo? Come on, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: initiative, right.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, question on roll 20. Is there a way to see the character sheet in Roll 20?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, so we use D&D Beyond.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, I did not buy the entire D&D set.
Kostadis Roussos: Twice. Alright. But there is a way to connect the two with a Chrome plugin called beyond 20.
Wade: Okay. Highly recommend.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And…
Kostadis Roussos: Which will, roll your… roll the character dice into the D&D Beyond.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right, yeah, that's why I was asking, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: D&D Beyond has created a…
Kostadis Roussos: That's the word I'm looking for.
Kostadis Roussos: Virtual tabletop.
Kostadis Roussos: Which I may at some point decide to switch to, but not today.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: understood.
Kostadis Roussos: It does have… it has some, like, nifty properties in particular around, generating encounters. All right.
David Mendenhall: When are we switching to Discord?
Kostadis Roussos: Because Gary still works at Google.
David Mendenhall: We have to wait until he's done? Is that really the case?
Wade: That's what I was hurt here, yeah.
Gary Young: Alright, what, what Discord server or whatever?
Wade: We just make one.
Gary Young: Alright.
Gary Young: Who's got that action item?
Kostadis Roussos: I will create…
David Mendenhall: Wade.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, Curtis?
David Mendenhall: I'll create a Discord export.
Kostadis Roussos: I will create a Discord server.
David Mendenhall: Oh, okay, Castanos.
Gary Young: huh?
Kostadis Roussos: In fact, I have one.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, it's called the Welcome to the Originals D&D Club.
David Mendenhall: The one that you use with all your other friends?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, it's the one that you are on.
Kostadis Roussos: Ari, do you have a… do folks have a, Discord ID? Wade, do you… what's your Discord ID?
Wade: Wade.
David Mendenhall: How many A's in that?
Wade: Live.
David Mendenhall: Wade with 5 A's.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, how do I add a member?
Wade: the link into the Google Chat.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Gary Young: Yeah, do that in the Google search.
Wade: I click your server and say, invite people.
Wade: And that'll give you a link that you can copy.
David Mendenhall: session, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Fair.
Kostadis Roussos: There.
Kostadis Roussos: I put it in the chat.
Wade: I got it.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.
Gary Young: Roll 20.
David Mendenhall: We chat.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, look at that.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Didn't you?
David Mendenhall: Login.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, it's… you're all in the pub, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Soma, let's see… loop it in.
Gary Young: Shall we start with people asking me what happened to Lucidus?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, then, yes, that is definitely what you should… that is definitely something we should start with.
Kostadis Roussos: Barthin is… Barthin's gone to his store, Linane has gone to her store, Adabra has gone to,
Kostadis Roussos: And Jenna here is, oh, noosing her wounds.
Kostadis Roussos: Using my loops.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so do you want to tell them what happened this time? The truth?
Gary Young: Yeah, they're asking me what happened to Lucidus, and I'll say, oh yeah, sister, what's her name? What's her name? Keldon.
David Mendenhall: okay.
Gary Young: Yeah, dude.
David Mendenhall: Did you kill the sister?
Gary Young: No, no. She said, that she would work with us to, defeat the Carver, so…
David Mendenhall: No!
Gary Young: We don't work with evil people.
Gary Young: What is this evil thing you're talking about?
David Mendenhall: is… let me put this in terms you can understand.
Gary Young: Enemy of…
David Mendenhall: We're not a power of Lysander.
Gary Young: Yeah. But he's enemy of our enemy. But she's enemy of our enemy.
David Mendenhall: No. She IS our enemy!
Gary Young: She is our enemy, but she is also enemy of our enemy, which provides good negotiation options.
David Mendenhall: I… I… I…
Kostadis Roussos: Did you explain?
David Mendenhall: I will have nothing to do with this.
Wade: Heh heh.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, so that means that…
Gary Young: She told us how to find the carver.
David Mendenhall: How do we find her, and kill her?
David Mendenhall: Did you…
Gary Young: Look at.
David Mendenhall: to attack?
Gary Young: And let her go?
David Mendenhall: You had her in your grasp, and you just let her walk away?
Gary Young: She offered a good negotiation deal.
David Mendenhall: Let me guess, she offered you some treasure too, didn't she?
Gary Young: Did she offer a starter?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she… she offered… she offered you, the reward that you were supposed… that she was gonna give to Lokutis, she offered you as a down payment for your negotiate… for your relationship.
Gary Young: Oh, we earned that, though.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: honey.
David Mendenhall: You can't earn stolen… how many times do I have to tell you people you can't earn stolen goods?
Gary Young: But that's…
Wade: You can earn it, you just can't keep it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: I need to go take a walk outside. I need some air and a cigarette.
David Mendenhall: I'm leaving the tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: You're leaving the tavern.
David Mendenhall: Oh, no!
David Mendenhall: Talk to the hand for a while.
Wade: My face has left the building.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay.
Gary Young: It happened to him, he had a very strange reaction.
Wade: He's a man of principle, don't you know?
Gary Young: What does that mean?
David Mendenhall: That's a good response.
Gary Young: The principles of self-defense, so that you have the survival of the fittest?
Wade: He doesn't think people should lose their possessions because they, you know, fell out of their pocket for some reason.
Gary Young: If they could be useful.
Wade: He thinks they belong to their original owner.
Gary Young: They're still alive.
Wade: I mean, you don't know that they're alive or not, he doesn't know they're alive or not. He needs to find out if they are.
Gary Young: Great. We will go on this overbright, adventure to figure out who these owners are, and if they are dead.
Wade: Yeah, that's the only problem. I think if we find out they're dead, he still has issues with taking the money.
Wade: I do kind of have a… draw a line there, but, he doesn't.
Kostadis Roussos: Jenna… Jenna Roscoe is looking at you, and then two… two… two of the villagers show up while you guys are having this debate, and… and say, are you?
Kostadis Roussos: Are you Lathander's cleric?
Wade: Yes!
Kostadis Roussos: And are you a believer in the purifying pain of the sun?
Gary Young: Yes, his brightness.
David Mendenhall: Altists.
Kostadis Roussos: We have been waiting for years for someone to see the truth that Lathander's glory is in feeling his pain while it sears you and brings you purity.
Gary Young: See the searing truth.
Kostadis Roussos: So they're like, so, so will you be establishing a chapel?
Gary Young: Cool. That's a good idea.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually…
Wade: It kind of is.
Kostadis Roussos: Will you be establishing a chapel?
Gary Young: At his…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, wh-wh-where?
Gary Young: Oh, we got some money here.
David Mendenhall: Jesus Christ.
Wade: Don't tell Vickers.
David Mendenhall: I'm not, I'm not in the.
Kostadis Roussos: room. He's like… What could possibly go wrong?
Wade: Oh, right!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, well, okay, I need to get some names, hold on. Alexa, turn on the lights.
Wade: I don't let us… your camera's off if you didn't know.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, it is? Sorry.
Gary Young: It doesn't bother me.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no.
Wade: make fun of me if I did it, so, you know.
Gary Young: Yeah, I would.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That is true.
Gary Young: I'm not sure what this arc is that will, teach her, overbright ways, but,
Gary Young: We're gonna have to figure this out.
Kostadis Roussos: Teacher, what, hold on, sorry.
David Mendenhall: So where are you gonna put the,
David Mendenhall: Where are you gonna put the chapel?
Gary Young: I don't know. Where is there a space in town?
David Mendenhall: And look at the map.
David Mendenhall: On roll 20.
Wade: And surely, one of these unlabeled buildings could just become the chapel, right?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, you could repurpose a building, or you could build a new building.
Wade: Well, do we have enough gold to build a new one? Enough free trade gold? I don't know!
Gary Young: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We could ask for a contribution from the faithful?
David Mendenhall: You probably would need me to do that.
Gary Young: Maybe I should work on, renovating this Trescendere Manor.
Wade: Who was.
Kostadis Roussos: The first one introduces himself as Brynn Bundlewine. He's fair-skinned.
Gary Young: bundle blind.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, Brynn Bundlein. And he introduces himself as a…
Kostadis Roussos: He's got… he has fair skin and a pageboy, haircut. And, you also see… Giles Slippershane.
Kostadis Roussos: Your footed eyes and restless hands.
Kostadis Roussos: And they're both very, kind of like.
Kostadis Roussos: Excited to see you. You also notice that they're very pale-skinned, and they've got a lot of sunburns.
Gary Young: Oh, okay.
Wade: Sort of the anti-Valfinays.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. And so they're kind of like, we've… we've heard… we've heard that, that we've heard that you too believe in the pain, and the purifying pain, and the religious ecstasy that comes from worshipping Lathander's pain.
David Mendenhall: Is skin cancer a thing in the D&D universe?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sure. Yeah.
Wade: Most people don't live that long.
Gary Young: He certainly, forgotten Realms, and I think he's also Greyhawk, isn't he? Or is there a translation?
Kostadis Roussos: There's a different god there.
Gary Young: Yeah. But it's still a sun god, right? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so, so, so he goes, take this, we have heard that you are, are, our one, our, the first one goes, the first guy goes.
Kostadis Roussos: We have heard of you. We heard rumors of a drow who worships Lathander, and we thought, only a drow could understand this… this message that we believe in, that it is through pain, like…
David Mendenhall: Let me go.
Gary Young: Yes. Their first orders will be to, clean up this Trescendo Manor.
Gary Young: It is now our new temple.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: Trustendo Manor.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, oh, Trescendor Manor, you want us to go clean that? That will be our manor.
Kostadis Roussos: Harbin, who happens to be around. Yes. You know, shows up, and .
David Mendenhall: And the Privy Council has voted that the Tresunder Manor will be the new chapel to the god Lathander.
David Mendenhall: Thank you for your support.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, well, you're not there right now. So Harbin says, did I hear that you're interested in turning the,
Kostadis Roussos: Tresander Manor into a religious, building?
Gary Young: That is correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I think that's a fantastic idea.
Gary Young: Great, you can help too.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. But, you know, currently that property is in receivership, and, you know, a small fee would be required to clear up the paperwork.
Gary Young: What? Possession is 9 tenths of the law, right?
David Mendenhall: The corruption in this town!
Wade: In this party? No.
Kostadis Roussos: He noticed you're not here, right?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I'm not here, yes, I'm still appalled.
Kostadis Roussos: Harbin's taking advantage of the fact that you're not…
David Mendenhall: I'm sure he is.
Kostadis Roussos: It's like, Valfinay, look, I think, I think the… I think the Privy Council and I could get to an arrangement where we could give it to you for a very small fee.
Gary Young: Do I feel like I need to purchase it, or do I feel like I just appropriated?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he said, appropriate… well, she goes, you wouldn't want… you wouldn't want the Privy Council to accuse you of stealing it now, would you?
Gary Young: Keepin'.
David Mendenhall: signed, I lead the Privy Council.
Gary Young: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He's on the Privy Council. So, now, if you were to do this, this could be a private matter that the entire council doesn't need to be exposed to.
Gary Young: Is this, is this the way things happen in the Overbrate?
Wade: Sometimes.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, you know, I think of it as… He pauses, overbright?
Gary Young: Yes, the overbright.
Kostadis Roussos: What is…
Gary Young: That's all this.
David Mendenhall: It's kind of the.
Gary Young: Gloriously bright sun, paint fills up.
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, Harbin goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that's… that's actually quite clever, is that… I didn't… I didn't know that. Wouldn't you know? Overbrite, I think I… I think I… yes, this is how things are done in the overbright.
Gary Young: And I'm looking to Wade to help me translate.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a deal we make. You help me, I help you.
Gary Young: Oh, yes.
Gary Young: Deals.
Gary Young: Yes, I understand.
Wade: You get deals.
Kostadis Roussos: It is… you know, this is arrangements, it's a… it's a… the town needs some money to, I don't know, do beautification of sorts, and so I could very easily arrange for the paperwork to be,
Kostadis Roussos: Pass the property on to you.
Wade: This is a good thing.
Gary Young: This is a good thing. Oh, okay.
Wade: I mean, well, good in quotes. Again, Vukradin probably won't approve, but… he doesn't need to know.
Gary Young: He doesn't need to know.
Wade: Does not need to know.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: Things are done here.
Kostadis Roussos: Habrin goes, yes.
Wade: For better or for worse, yes.
Gary Young: The editor will be pleased.
David Mendenhall: Rubbery, what do you say as you observe this whole thing?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm sort of scratching my head. I don't think I'm smart enough to understand what's going on, really.
Kostadis Roussos: And, and, and Spider-Man, by the way, Harbin's telling Spider-Man to keep bringing you beers.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh yeah, I'm pretty happy.
Kostadis Roussos: Harbin's telling… is kind of going like this to Harv… to… to Spider-Man, and like that, to get you to get some beers.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so Spider-Man, you know, every time you're finished drinking, Spider-Man shows up with more people.
Wade: That guy.
Gary Young: Oh, keep on drinking!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Ben.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: In the Uthgart barbarian ways, and isn't all just communal property?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so…
David Mendenhall: What was the… what was the fee to be here with the.
Wade: What was the fee? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: 50 gold pieces.
David Mendenhall: And how much…
Gary Young: Her sister, what's her name? Layla?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: How much money do we get from Sister of Lula?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, 200 gold pieces.
Wade: Oh, so we have that lying around, alright. That's convenient.
David Mendenhall: Did you, so, put the… add the difference to blood money?
Gary Young: Sure.
Gary Young: Lug money. Alright.
Gary Young: Plus 150.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Gary Young: And we'll have to make sure that we decorate the Church of Lothander with, lots of, spikes and chains.
Wade: just want a bunch of windows?
Gary Young: Yeah, well, I mean, we shouldn't cover over the roof.
Wade: Skylights, you need actual skylights.
Gary Young: Me and Charlie, too.
Kostadis Roussos: You'll notice it on the map it now says, Temple of Lathander, Searing Pain of Justice.
Gary Young: Nice.
Wade: Why don't… where do I…
Kostadis Roussos: So if you… if you go, you should see it, right?
Wade: I don't think I… Mr. Yas…
David Mendenhall: I see.
Gary Young: That's it.
Wade: Oh, I'm just blind. Oh, there it is. Oh, it's in red at the right far.
David Mendenhall: Crawl whale.
Wade: Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so… so you've now… you've now have… that now belongs to you.
Gary Young: Alright.
Gary Young: We're well on our way to…
Gary Young: I miss when we just ran a play.
Kostadis Roussos: What? You don't… you don't approve, or…
Wade: No, I'm kidding, it's…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see if I can get…
Kostadis Roussos: That would work better, yeah. Temple of Lothander, Searing Pain of Justice.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? That's…
Wade: more legible, thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, that would be the other one. The red one was not really logical. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okie dokie.
David Mendenhall: the Wren and Giles are off to, the temple to… Spruce it up.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so that… they're gonna be doing that for a few days. The sprucing up is gonna cost some money, Gary.
Gary Young: And they're not paying?
David Mendenhall: pay him before I get back.
Kostadis Roussos: First of all, I mean, not for them, that they're doing it, the labor is free, but they need to buy stuff, right?
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, like, beams, like, you don't… like, construction material.
Kostadis Roussos: So they're gonna say, you know, 25 gold pieces, we'll get it set up correctly.
Gary Young: Weight, is this appropriate?
Wade: Seems a little high, but… Should be able to haggle him down.
Gary Young: You will cut trees.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, it's right next.
Kostadis Roussos: to a forest. He goes, yes, it's a forest.
David Mendenhall: It's true!
Kostadis Roussos: Right, which is… but, you know, we have to buy… there's, like, there's… we have to buy furniture. I mean, yes, well, we'll do a lot of the hard work. Your… your… your,
Kostadis Roussos: Your worshipfulness.
Gary Young: Your grace will do.
Kostadis Roussos: Your grace, your grace… your grace, but that person can…
Gary Young: No, no.
Wade: tenants now.
Kostadis Roussos: your pain?
Gary Young: Reverend Mother. That was the, what do they say in, in the drought communities? It's, the…
Kostadis Roussos: Matron Mother.
Gary Young: Patriot Mother, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Nature and mother.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you're gonna go with the.
Gary Young: Patron mother of Luthanter. There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: Whoa!
David Mendenhall: I'm sure when Lathander finally connects with you, you're high enough level for the comeuppance.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, do you consider that this is part of Lefender's global vision here?
David Mendenhall: It's not.
Kostadis Roussos: Have you considered the possibility that, you know, he's testing his religious followers?
Wade: Mathander works in mysterious ways.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, that's it.
Wade: like I'm putting any undead in his temple. Not yet.
Gary Young: Not yet.
Gary Young: I guess that's… That's true.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's put Bryn…
David Mendenhall: Do you have that spell yet? You'll get there.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Brendan Giles, let's just put Brendan Giles there so we don't forget that they exist.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Brennan Giles are, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: are very happy to be putting together the temple. Harbin is very happy that it will now, you know, the Sander Mander, which has been in a state of disrepair, will be built. You know, money… and Jenna turns to,
Kostadis Roussos: turns to you and says… turns to the three of you and says, see, this is what I mean about how money, when you take it as adventures and then put it back into the community, it becomes clean money. See how it becomes… it becomes… it's not really blood money, you're returning it to the people, right?
David Mendenhall: Almost as if it's been laundered.
Gary Young: We're doing well.
Wade: Washed clean.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: See, we're not…
Wade: That's what you need to convince.
Kostadis Roussos: I just… I just want you to see how this works, so that you could perhaps, you know, reach out to Vukriddin a little bit, and make him see the… the… how this all works.
Wade: He's young, he's got a lot to learn, give him time.
David Mendenhall: I'm gonna be running.
Gary Young: in this town.
Wade: Yes. I mean, you probably are destined for great things.
Wade: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Alright, I'm gonna wander back into the…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you wandered back into…
David Mendenhall: Cigarette is out. Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Feeling thirsty. Alright. Back in the tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so nighttime passes, unless there's anything else.
David Mendenhall: So nothing happened while I was gone, right? Did you guys change your mind about all this nonsense about partnering with evil people?
Gary Young: We're just gonna found a temple here, because, like, there's not.
David Mendenhall: I'm in the temple?
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: That's a good thing, right?
David Mendenhall: That's a good thing.
Wade: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Where'd you get the money to do that?
Kostadis Roussos: Harbin says… Harbin interrupts my, my, my, my, Vukra didn't… I just want you to know that this was a donation made by the community.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Wade: No, he's helping.
David Mendenhall: Compound time, something good happened around here.
Kostadis Roussos: I think the community felt that this would be a good step forward and, you know, bring…
David Mendenhall: Maybe I won't have to replace you next week.
David Mendenhall: Alright.
Gary Young: Anybody believes in left-hander.
Wade: How about donating a free round of beer? Spider-Man, I think that's an excellent idea.
Wade: I'll… Can drink to that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Spider-Man shows up with the beers, hands them over. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: The morning, you wait, you go to sleep, you wake up in the morning, and you just see there's a bunch of quests that you're supposed.
David Mendenhall: I would like to talk to Sir Karen.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, what do you want to ask him?
David Mendenhall: How are you doing in tracking down the rightful owners of all this
David Mendenhall: treasure we've found that needs to be returned. You said you were working on that for us.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, at a game, Castanis hasn't figured that out yet, so…
David Mendenhall: Bill? Sir Karen, what are you doing?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, look, by the time… so, look, he goes… so Costata says… let me see what his status…
Kostadis Roussos: Sec this… I need to check something out.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: did the Butter Skulline. He goes, Sir Kalen goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so he goes, well, I should be able to help you with that.
Kostadis Roussos: In a few days, the message I sent up to Neverwinter should bring me… should bring me back some information in a few days.
David Mendenhall: Okay, sounds good.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And, in the meantime, you may want to go check out what's been going on at Mountain Toes.
David Mendenhall: Oh yeah, it's Mountain Toes, that…
David Mendenhall: Does seem like the next place to go… There was also Logger's Camp.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Loggers Camp, Harbin… Harbin hears the words Logger's Camp and gets very excited because, that's, something that hit for his brother, that he wants with his brother.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that correct? No.
David Mendenhall: We just need to carry some supplies to the camp.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Gary Young: And isn't that in the direction of the curver?
David Mendenhall: I don't know, you tell me.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Nice strike.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Kayla said she would give you some information in a few days, so…
Kostadis Roussos: You don't actually know where the carver is.
Gary Young: O.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: So we need to either escort some guy to a gold mine, or carry a bunch of supplies into the forest.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I vote for carrying supplies to the forest.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Gary Young: Yeah, he's big and can carry things, that's great.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah, well, you know… And I'm a sucker for the fall.
Wade: forest.
David Mendenhall: I guess Harbin just did me a solid by, you know, donating this new chapel, so I guess I should try to help them out.
David Mendenhall: The naivete just keeps going.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, I like the man, he handles free beer.
Kostadis Roussos: He's a big believer, like, you know, why, why, why, alright, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so it goes,
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Harbin says that you need to step by Barthin's provisions to collect the provisions.
Kostadis Roussos: To go… To…
David Mendenhall: Wasn't I supposed to buy a rapier, or something like that?
Kostadis Roussos: If you want.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, how much does that cost?
Kostadis Roussos: Lenini says, standard prices, so…
David Mendenhall: Alright, I will look it up.
Wade: Pretty cheap, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Whatever, whatever the standard price for that is.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, it's this morning.
David Mendenhall: 5…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: How much provisions are we talking about, by the way, that we need to carry? Do we need some sort of carriage or something, or…
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so, so you, you go to Barth, Barthen.
Kostadis Roussos: What does Barthin do? Barthin says…
Kostadis Roussos: Where is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Wait.
Kostadis Roussos: Why didn't I click on this site? Did I not click on the right thing? We're going to the loggers, right? Is that what we said?
Wade: Yeah. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Okay, so you have to go to Barthen to find out.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'll go.
David Mendenhall: No, we can all go.
Wade: Yeah, it's probably gonna be a lot to carry.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yep.
Kostadis Roussos: When you arrive to pick up the supplies, Barthin is there, and he tells you that his clerks have filled two creeks with supplies as he hands you a sheet of parchment, upon which is written.
Kostadis Roussos: An inventory of the crate's constants. Foodstuffs such as dried meats, blocks of cheese, and loaves of bread, as well as casks of ale and flasks of oil.
Kostadis Roussos: The two heavy crates are loaded onto a two-wheeled cart pulled by Knox.
Kostadis Roussos: Barthinen says, Box's name is Vincent.
Kostadis Roussos: And I'll expect to see him and the cart returned. Thanks!
Gary Young: Do we need the cart and the ox?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, it's two crates. Yeah, that's a.
Kostadis Roussos: Harry. Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I need at least one hand to fight if we meet somebody.
Gary Young: You need to shut it down, if there's a bike.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And hold on, those crates have bread and cheese and no wine? That doesn't seem right.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh!
Kostadis Roussos: He says, wait!
Kostadis Roussos: Did you say you wanted some wine? Brewberry?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Absolutely. Cheese, bread, you gotta have wine.
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, well,
Kostadis Roussos: Turns out there is a hunting lodge on the way that you could stop at.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: A hunting lodge.
Kostadis Roussos: It sells very fine wine.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, I turn to the group and say, what do you say, guys? We go get ourselves some fine wine with this bread and cheese.
Wade: Salma's down for wine.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Alright, so I'm just going to show you where that is here.
Kostadis Roussos: You should be able to see it now.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you see it?
Gary Young: Wow, that was pretty far away.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, it's a bit of a hike.
Gary Young: So, we needed to escort someone to a gold mine, right?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: Didn't we need to escort someone to go?
David Mendenhall: other quests. We're gonna do.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, man.
David Mendenhall: I'm first.
Wade: Oh, I see. Oh, wow, that is way out there.
Gary Young: The gold mine is kind of on the way, though.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you could do both, you don't have to do… you don't have to do one… you could do, like, them together. It's not like you have to do one, come back, do the other.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, but I mean, do we take the cart and Vincent to the gold mine? Doesn't seem… super safe.
Wade: It could get a little, you know, lost, damaged along the way, I mean.
Wade: There, we've encountered many a bandit.
Gary Young: Sure. Just, putting it out there.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, to, to the loggers, to the.
Wade: There, there.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: First up…
Wade: Thank you, buddy.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's true.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so that's about a 2-day's journey.
Wade: 50 miles, yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Today's journey.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Do we have provisions for two days? That's not in the crate, I mean.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming you have, rations.
Wade: We, yeah, we don't usually track that stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, we don't track arrows and rations.
Kostadis Roussos: And only when narratively appropriate do we track encumbrance.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I mean, booster.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: pretty big, I eat a lot, so…
David Mendenhall: I believe we have one.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: arrangement.
David Mendenhall: Various bags of holding and such.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I see.
Kostadis Roussos: Although they've been at… No, no, there's been a curious shortage of bags of holding.
Gary Young: Yeah, we don't have that.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You don't…
Wade: I want another bomb going off, and shit.
Kostadis Roussos: There's… there are some curious… there have been some curious problems about finding bags of holding in interplanar…
David Mendenhall: Right, right.
Kostadis Roussos: What is it? Interplanar export? No.
Kostadis Roussos: I can't remember. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, I presume you're… sorry, we're going to the hunting lodge first, or the, l.
Wade: Haunting lodge.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Wine. Yes, we got wine.
Wade: Drew Berry's thirsty.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Absolutely.
Kostadis Roussos: to the…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Always.
Wade: Anyway, it's nice to break up the monotony, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay, so, before you go,
Kostadis Roussos: what's his, barthen explains, the Falking Hunting Lodge is a sanctuary in the center of the heart of Neverwinterwood. It's,
Kostadis Roussos: It's… it was maintained by Falcon the Hunter.
Kostadis Roussos: He offers his services as a guide to those nobles, most of them who wouldn't last long in the forest without his protection and survivor kill skills. He abhors city lives, preferring a touristic existence and simple pleasures. His lodge has all the creature comforts he requires.
Kostadis Roussos: He has 2 retainers.
Kostadis Roussos: And he says this is a… it is in addition to a hunting lodge, then the main house, it includes a guest house for visitors, a conjoined stable house and smithy, an outhouse and pens to hold the falcon's lion livestock. You're free to stay.
Kostadis Roussos: And he says, I, I would recommend you go there, and the opera is a wonderful
Kostadis Roussos: Private room in the main lodge, or a modest fee?
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Maybe you could send them a note ahead of time, tell them we're coming, and who we are, and how awesome we are.
David Mendenhall: We should have a say in all those things?
Kostadis Roussos: Roll your persuasion.
David Mendenhall: A minimum 15.
David Mendenhall: But if you'd like me to roll…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, because I want to see whether you get a natural 20, because I want to see what else, whether you…
David Mendenhall: 15.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he says, well, he goes, well, I can't really go, but he scribbles down a note and hands it to you.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: It is a bit of a journey, and I do have my store to manage.
David Mendenhall: Okay. Did he, like, sign it, put his seal on it? Yeah, it's clear that it's actually legit from him, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, it's a logistics.
Wade: I don't you.
David Mendenhall: Alright, I'll take it out of that works.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? He says, alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sounds like maybe you can entertain the patrons once we get there, if you can…
David Mendenhall: While we're in town, do we need to sell anything?
Gary Young: We have my old chain shirt to sell, and then some blood money stuff.
David Mendenhall: Go ahead and administer.
Gary Young: Why didn't really sell that at Family?
David Mendenhall: I'm sure it's organic, the rest is blood.
Gary Young: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, go ahead, sell.
Gary Young: I assume the change.
David Mendenhall: Oh, and can I persuade for a better deal, please? Minimum 15.
Wade: Boom.
Gary Young: I assume the chain shirt that I brought with me from the Underdark is, not blood… blood leisure.
David Mendenhall: I probably wouldn't question that one, yeah.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: You assured me that it was yours.
Wade: Heh.
Gary Young: That's definitely mine.
Wade: see negative prominence.
Kostadis Roussos: Definitely mine!
David Mendenhall: I now…
Wade: It's Schrodinger's blood money? I don't know, like…
Kostadis Roussos: So you arrive at the Falcon Hunting Lodge.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: I think we have some gems and stuff, too, you could sell, Gary.
Gary Young: I don't know, I mean, it looks like some of this is blood money, though.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Gary Young: I don't know if we want to sell this spellbook just yet, but…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Until we find the rightful owners, what do we usually do with all the loot?
Wade: We just leave it in the inventory.
David Mendenhall: Hauling it around until they can return it.
Gary Young: Alright.
Wade: Did they not show you…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: With us, alright.
Wade: Blood Money flag in the, loot chart.
David Mendenhall: We're pretty sure that Brewberry carries an entire, barrel of wine with him everywhere he goes, Stefan, so…
David Mendenhall: Just right on the right shoulder, he doesn't need both shoulders.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Gary Young: Isn't there, like, some trope, like, anime trope, for, like, having, like, a keg on your back, or something like that? Like, a small keg?
Wade: Oh, there are definitely a bunch of anime types of that, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Give me that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you arrive at… D.
Kostadis Roussos: Falcon Lodge.
David Mendenhall: Wow, that's it? We just made it? No problems? Yeah, it was great. All the, like, magic of Neverwinter Wood and all that stuff didn't affect us?
Kostadis Roussos: Not this time.
Wade: Even the cart didn't slow us down, like…
David Mendenhall: We weren't… We weren't confounded as navigators, we weren't…
David Mendenhall: The ancient ruins weren't obscured to us.
Kostadis Roussos: No, because…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Stay away from the shrewberries, you know?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Because they give you nasty stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, no, no, I mean, sometimes… sometimes you arrive there, it's kind of a disappointment, almost. Like, there was, like, nothing happened. It was, like, it was just a boring, you know, two-day trip.
David Mendenhall: Wasn't boring.
Wade: It's a nice nature hike.
David Mendenhall: Sang songs, we were out in nature…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, see, it was right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Good luck.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that's true.
David Mendenhall: drank some. We didn't steal anything.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope, not, not a single thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, a thin fog surrounds a…
Kostadis Roussos: Fortified compound standing in a clearing on the east side of the narrow Viv River.
Kostadis Roussos: A 10-foot-high log palisade surrounds the compound, whose main building is a two-story stone with a fair with a high-pitched roof, gables, window shutters, and a stone chimney. Attached to the main building is a blocky tower of gray stone, its high roof lined with battlements.
Kostadis Roussos: Other structures include a two-story stable house, and a gatehouse whose flat roof is enclosed by iron railings. A stone bridge spans the river, ending before an open door set into the gatehouse's outer wall. Mounted next to the door is a bell with a short rope hanging from its clappers.
Wade: Ring the bell, I think.
Kostadis Roussos: You ring the bell?
Kostadis Roussos: Note.
Wade: We're not gonna break it, are we?
Kostadis Roussos: No, I hope not.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I wonder why they have such a fence. You said a 10 feet high?
Kostadis Roussos: Depends.
David Mendenhall: Is there a… is there a map?
David Mendenhall: I didn't put you on the map yet.
Wade: Yeah, we're still on the world map.
Kostadis Roussos: There.
Wade: Recticulating splines…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: It's like a battle map.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I know, I'm gonna get rid of the… since there's no…
Kostadis Roussos: This is supposed to be somewhat of a not, violent place. Let me just do something here.
Wade: Spoiler!
David Mendenhall: Ringing the bell, that's the plan?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm back.
Wade: I mean, that's my plan, unless you've got a better idea.
David Mendenhall: We could just…
Gary Young: Is there anything amiss? I mean, if there is nothing amiss, then…
Kostadis Roussos: No, there is nothing amiss.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Wade: Not yet. He didn't ask us to roll perception, it must be safe.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you open… do you walk up and ring the doorbell?
David Mendenhall: 19.
Kostadis Roussos: It turns out there is literally nothing bad going on.
Wade: Ring the damn bell.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright. Alright.
David Mendenhall: Go for it. Go for it, Soma.
Wade: Alright, Soma rings the bell. Hello?
Kostadis Roussos: Well…
Kostadis Roussos: That's what the problem is. Alright, hearing the bell. The bell was rung, and what happens? Need to get… what's his name?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to, need to get a commoner.
Wade: For it's worth, this is all fog of war inside.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
Wade: just…
Kostadis Roussos: We can fix that, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Corwin, this guy looks you over, says, who are you?
Wade: I'm Selma.
David Mendenhall: Note, hand him the note.
Wade: Oh, yeah, definitely.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, he looks at it and goes, Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: You're from… you're… Barthen sent you. Well, come in, come in!
Kostadis Roussos: I'm, I'm sure, The Falcon Hunter will want to chat with you.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. He's like, so.
David Mendenhall: wanna…
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: Stand in the corner, it's well guarded.
Kostadis Roussos: You're standing in the corner?
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: What news do you have from the logging cap?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know, I don't do the nose… I don't do the news. Let me get the falcon hunter, and he can talk to you.
David Mendenhall: Who are you? What's your name?
Kostadis Roussos: My name is, my name is… Corwin.
David Mendenhall: What's it again?
David Mendenhall: Owen!
Kostadis Roussos: Corwin, my name's Corwin, although my friends called me Chef. You're not my friends yet, so you can call me Corwin.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, so…
David Mendenhall: Do you do a lot of cooking, Corwin?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know, I'm the… I cook the meals here, yeah, that would be what I do. I also do.
David Mendenhall: So you're the chef.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you could say that.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Gary Young: Do you also make wine?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Can you tell me about the wine?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, let me get the Falcon Hunter. He's the one you really want to be talking about.
Wade: He really doesn't want to talk to us.
David Mendenhall: No, not Falcon Hunter, Falcon the Hunter.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Falcon the Hunter, he's the guy you want to talk to, not me.
David Mendenhall: And Druid.
Gary Young: I love a Cyprus.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
David Mendenhall: Another Druid.
Wade: Those are full-on mutton chops, dude.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm.
Gary Young: Alright, can you guys see him?
Wade: Yes, we see him.
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, my goodness, my goodness!
Kostadis Roussos: Guests! Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful, wonderful. It's been a while since I've seen any guests.
David Mendenhall: Alright, I guess I should move in and charm him.
Wade: Hey, work your magic, face.
David Mendenhall: Do all the talking.
Kostadis Roussos: You, you are…
David Mendenhall: The letter, present the letter.
Kostadis Roussos: My goodness, my good friend Barthen invited you here. That is an excellent, excellent, excellent activity for me to hear.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, we're on our way to the logger's camp.
Kostadis Roussos: You're on your way to the logger's camp?
Wade: I mean, I assume.
Kostadis Roussos: And he sees the cart we have in tow, right? Yeah, he goes, well, you know, I… first of all, I think you should spend the night here.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll have a wonderful meal.
Kostadis Roussos: I… and if… if…
David Mendenhall: We have a band!
David Mendenhall: Can we perform for you?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that would be spectacular!
David Mendenhall: Sure, happy to.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at Valfinay. He goes, I don't mean to be rude.
Wade: Oh, good, I'm glad you're not rude.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I… I… you are a… a drow, yes?
David Mendenhall: Oh, yes. So much racism.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, no, it happens to be that I have another drow staying with me, and I think she would be delighted to have dinner with you.
Gary Young: Can we handle two drows? Okay.
David Mendenhall: I'm kind of curious, like, is that okay? You wanna have dinner with her?
David Mendenhall: Arrival?
Gary Young: That's her name.
Kostadis Roussos: You know I don't recall it off the top of my head.
Wade: He's trying to set you up.
Wade: Enough of the chit-chat, tell us about the wine.
David Mendenhall: Priorities.
Wade: I love a good barbarian.
Kostadis Roussos: And you are… your name is, sir?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm the wine drinker. Tell me about the wine.
Kostadis Roussos: It goes well.
David Mendenhall: Blueberry, he's Brewberry. Good friend, good friend.
Kostadis Roussos: goes, Brewberry, I keep some of the best wine in the area in my cellar.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, good, I'm thirsty.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, excellent! I must warn you, it's not the cheapest wine.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Not where you.
David Mendenhall: Friends of…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What are you implying?
David Mendenhall: We are friends of Barthlone, whatever his name is.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, yes, yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And we will entertain.
David Mendenhall: You know, such a good friend.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, well, you know, I could be a Falcon, Falcon goes, I can't give you an infinite supply, but certainly I could give you a few bottles, and if the bard here was to play some dunes tonight to keep us entertained, I'm certain I could bring out some more wine to keep us all pleasantly happy.
Wade: I don't think you can stop him.
David Mendenhall: Happy to play for beer.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I sort of tower over him, and I'm like, make that barrels, and you got it here.
David Mendenhall: Intimidation?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Intimidating.
Kostadis Roussos: He kind of looks at you, and he sort of laughs heartily, and he says, well, well, well, well.
Kostadis Roussos: I think, I think we will be good friends here. I think we will be good friends here.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, good friends.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so he brings you to the dinner. So, he, he says, well, let's… and so, you know, a few hours later, he goes, and while you're here, you might as well just sit down, relax.
Kostadis Roussos: Check, check out, and we will have dinner in the dining room!
Wade: That's an appropriate place to eat.
David Mendenhall: Look around while we're here.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So I don't really relax, though. I turn to him and I say, why such a big fence around this tavern?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yes, good co- good question.
Kostadis Roussos: He says, that is an excellent question.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, ever since the dragon showed up.
Kostadis Roussos: The orcs have left their mountain homes and have now descended into the valley.
Kostadis Roussos: And I've seen more orcs of wood… in the woods of lakes. Ugly, ugly brutes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Gary Young: When he said he stopped numbers.
David Mendenhall: out here, just, you know, because it's kind of a small space, and they would probably perform out.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, he goes… he wants you to perform in the dining room.
Kostadis Roussos: So, very…
David Mendenhall: It's gonna be really loud.
Kostadis Roussos: The dining room is very large.
David Mendenhall: It's not that big.
Wade: Is this not the dining room?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that's a dining room. That's like a 40 by 6… 80 foot area.
David Mendenhall: Alright, alright, I'll follow.
Wade: Really?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So where do those stairs be?
Kostadis Roussos: but…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You see stairs on the map? Where do they lead?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, here, I'll hear, I'll, I'll, to the seller.
Wade: The wine cellar.
David Mendenhall: The wine cellar.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, he… they don't.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so, this is the dining room, and upstairs is his bedroom… is,
Kostadis Roussos: is his deluxe guest bed… his deluxe guest bedroom, his personal bedroom.
Kostadis Roussos: That's what's upstairs.
David Mendenhall: Are you staying in the deluxe guest bedroom?
Kostadis Roussos: He, he goes, I… he goes, well, if the music is good, why not?
David Mendenhall: 16, yeah, definitely.
David Mendenhall: Dangles.
Gary Young: Did you do the performance check?
Wade: That was persuasion.
David Mendenhall: Sure, we can do a performance check.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
David Mendenhall: 22.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Good night.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Arrogant.
Gary Young: What sort of music were you playing this time?
David Mendenhall: Pop death metal? Isn't that what we do?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay, alright.
Gary Young: Our usual, alright.
David Mendenhall: the usual.
Gary Young: So, do I need to do my singing check here?
Kostadis Roussos: So you have to do your singing.
David Mendenhall: Go ahead.
Gary Young: Alright, so…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So we, so we noticed, you know, the…
David Mendenhall: I think you're… you're a little off, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god.
David Mendenhall: Why don't you, you know, it was good.
Wade: Alright, Yoko, take a backseat.
David Mendenhall: Now take it and get go-go.
David Mendenhall: I'll go.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So while all this good entertainment takes place, I ask if there are people standing watch around the fence as well. The fence is good, but if there are orcs, who's standing watch?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, you know, I don't really need… it's like, they know not to come here, and I've got a… he pauses, and I am…
Kostadis Roussos: They know not to trouble me, but if they trouble me, they'll be dead orcs.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Gary Young: This is what topics.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he's a very arrogant guy. Kind of has that look of, like, you know, they won't mess with me.
Wade: It's getting so raised by the end of the campaign, isn't it?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Wade: This is gonna be so burned down by the end of the campaign.
Kostadis Roussos: He then explains, although, he pauses as, as so… so, let's see, so, so this is the dining room. Let's see what else…
David Mendenhall: Brave of you to think that it's gonna last that long, Wade.
Wade: I said by the end of the campaign.
Gary Young: The carver doesn't bother him here?
Kostadis Roussos: You didn't ask about that.
Gary Young: The last time. The carburet doesn't bother you here?
David Mendenhall: is the carver.
David Mendenhall: Dun dun dun.
Gary Young: As he's been hiring orcs.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, the carver? Who's the carver?
Wade: Nice to know.
David Mendenhall: He's a bandit leader.
Gary Young: Edit later.
David Mendenhall: been terrorizing… People around these parts.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, oh, yes, I've heard rumors about this, this, this man.
David Mendenhall: We have, we have our friend with us, what's his name?
Kostadis Roussos: Cor… Corbin.
Wade: Barben, yeah.
Gary Young: Permit, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Wait, another… oh, there's Corbin.
Wade: Performance.
David Mendenhall: is with Corwin.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade: I thought it was Horow.
David Mendenhall: That was… that's lame.
Wade: Well, you know, I didn't, like, do it.
Kostadis Roussos: or at, Roku.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you know, he says, oh, a bandit.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that would explain some things.
Gary Young: Explain why.
David Mendenhall: Like, what?
Kostadis Roussos: All the banditry?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, well, no, I mean, I thought it was only the orcs, but I have noticed that the orcs have done… there's been… there has been a few more, what's the word I'm looking for?
David Mendenhall: More organized than usual.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that would be exactly what I was about to say. They seem a little bit more organized.
Wade: Yeah, they lay traps and other weird things now.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, yes, yes, and… but that may explain why they have… the orcs appear to be in league with some evil half-orcs.
Gary Young: Evil half-orcs.
Wade: evil half-orcs.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, there's some evil half-orcs that dwell southwest of here.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Gary Young: Are they a problem for you?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, not really, but they do dwell in a ruined stone manse overgrown with vines roughly 10 miles from here.
David Mendenhall: Are they the legal owners of that?
Wade: No.
Gary Young: Do you know who it is?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, it was abandoned.
Gary Young: How's it been?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Gary Young: So then they are the.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, shit.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah.
Wade: Squatters, right?
David Mendenhall: That's not how that works.
Gary Young: No, pretty sweet.
David Mendenhall: Delphina, you still don't understand the overbright.
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, look, he goes, I, you know, he's like, there's… yes, they are. But, you know, I don't think they're much of a broad… they don't bother me, they don't bother me too much. And if they were to do anything, I could handle them, but, you know, just… they… they do… they do their…
David Mendenhall: Yeah, you seem quite powerful.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know, I've been here for many years, I'm…
David Mendenhall: Do you ever go out, and… do you ever do any adventuring?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that's like…
David Mendenhall: hype.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, those days are long past me.
David Mendenhall: Why?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, because I like having my… I like doing what I'm doing now.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I, you know, I retired from adventuring.
David Mendenhall: Retired from my bed.
Kostadis Roussos: Deposit's good.
Wade: It's an arrow to the knee, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, he pauses and says, you know, I learned something about adventuring.
Kostadis Roussos: There's not many old adventurers.
Kostadis Roussos: There's many dead adventure.
Kostadis Roussos: There's young adventurers.
David Mendenhall: A lot of young adventurers.
Kostadis Roussos: There's young adventurers, and there's retired old adventurers. There's no old adventurers who are still adventuring.
Wade: Excuse me.
David Mendenhall: Wellness.
Wade: What do you make of me?
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses… he goes… he looks at you and goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I… he's that, like, you know, he's kind of, like, realized that he's put his foot in it, and he's a bit, you know, like… he's like, I didn't mean it, blah blah blah.
Gary Young: I'm sure Valfin is at least 70 or 80, but she doesn't consider herself old, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. So he's like, so I, you know, in my experience, it's best to, take the point of view that adventurers should retire once they've made a pile of money.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, it's not about how long you live your life, it's how you live your life.
Kostadis Roussos: I completely agree, and I have chosen to live my life as a…
Kostadis Roussos: owner of a proprietare in the wilderness, where I get to go hunting, and periodically have guests come over whom I help hunt, and I make money, and I take care of my animals, and I have fine wine, and drink… eat fine meals.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Except for the…
David Mendenhall: Hard one, so…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's glory.
David Mendenhall: I earn so much money.
Kostadis Roussos: What did… what'd you say?
David Mendenhall: Must have done a lot of noble quests to earn such money.
Kostadis Roussos: Does anybody warn him before he says the next sentence?
Wade: He's not in our party, he can stick his foot in his mouth all he wants.
David Mendenhall: What is he?
Gary Young: cut.
David Mendenhall: What's the response?
Wade: Is there something that I'm supposed to be catching with Insight here?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you're about to catch with Insight, that he may not know about Vukradin's, policy. Yeah, you definitely are about… you definitely pick up with Insight, that he's… he may suddenly start talking about treasures he plundered, monsters he killed…
Gary Young: Wait, so I pick up that he's gonna talk about that.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Gary Young: And that's normal to me, right?
Wade: Yes. Yes. And you don't… you don't quite understand what's going on with Vucherdin, so I don't, I don't think you would interrupt, but…
David Mendenhall: Continue.
David Mendenhall: you see the train coming, and you're like, I'm gonna stand right in the middle of the tracks.
Wade: I want to watch it come close.
Gary Young: Yeah, this is the right way.
Kostadis Roussos: I just want to make sure.
David Mendenhall: The light! It's so bright! It's coming trites for me!
Kostadis Roussos: And in Valfini's case, that would literally be what she would do.
David Mendenhall: Exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the falcon says, well, Vucra did, yes, I did, in fact, made quite a bit of money from adventuring.
Kostadis Roussos: why, there was this dragon that my group killed, and it had a large horde that we split four ways. And part of that horde is how I built this…
David Mendenhall: I'm playing!
Gary Young: I will not…
David Mendenhall: Whoa!
Gary Young: Yep, yep, yep, that sounds right.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he was like, it was… it was that horde that allowed me…
Wade: I'm gonna go.
David Mendenhall: Alright, we're done, we're not playing here.
David Mendenhall: I will not perform in this venue.
Wade: He goes, "'put, but, but, he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: That was many years ago. Now, I only do…
Wade: Here, let's see…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, he really doesn't pick up on it. He goes.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know what I said, but I want you to know that ever since then, I only take guests that pay for their fees, and you know, this is all a…
David Mendenhall: It wasn't enough that you had to steal from all those people killed by the dragon. You continue to take more money!
Gary Young: Wait, aren't we guests here?
Gary Young: Is this how we treat you? After long!
David Mendenhall: Extra.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: long.
Gary Young: By the way, there's supposed to be some drought here too, right?
Wade: Yes. You're gone.
David Mendenhall: cigarette.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gonna grab a cigarette? Alright.
David Mendenhall: I've seen that a lot lately.
Kostadis Roussos: Smoke back again.
Wade: Got him.
Kostadis Roussos: So, Booker Din grabs a guest. The Falcon Hunter looks at the rest of you with this kind of look of, like, so do the rest of you think I'm thieves? I'm a thief.
Gary Young: He has some strange ways.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Well…
Kostadis Roussos: If the rest of you don't think I'm a thief, I suppose I could forgive your friend here, but he will not be having any free wine.
Gary Young: Okay. Your wine, your choice.
David Mendenhall: to drink.
Kostadis Roussos: And then he pauses.
David Mendenhall: You don't need music.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, he pauses, he says, I've heard this rumor.
Kostadis Roussos: That's been going around about this new movement against adventurers using plunder.
Kostadis Roussos: It's all part… it's all part of some sort of attempt to disrupt the ruling elite and to force the imposition of law and order, and move away from the
Kostadis Roussos: Barbaric violence of adventuring.
Wade: Gets a bit.
Gary Young: Like the new economic system.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: It's like a new economic system.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he goes, I've heard these rumors, it's all nonsense, if you ask me. He goes, the purpose of adventurers is to adventure, to take the gold, and to plow it back into the communities, and to…
Wade: That's one way.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, return… who would.
Wade: The adventure can be the reward on its own, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, he goes, I couldn't.
David Mendenhall: Ew! I like that.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Soba, that is extremely wise, and obviously, a tortle of your wisdom will most definitively enjoy dinner tonight.
Wade: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, dinner arrives, and…
David Mendenhall: Let's see, I should go put my character where I really am. Definitely not…
Kostadis Roussos: I need to, I need to exit, need to exit a roll time.
David Mendenhall: I'm, sulking over here eating rations.
Kostadis Roussos: You're not… you're not gonna be, dancing, you're not gonna be singing? Is that what I'm hearing?
David Mendenhall: No.
Wade: He's not gonna play, no, he's not gonna play for a blood money.
Wade: Or, you know, a thief, whatever.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: But it's performed already, right? So, we sort of…
David Mendenhall: I'm done, I'm done, the set's over.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he's, he's… he plays.
David Mendenhall: It was a great set, too.
Wade: It was.
David Mendenhall: Wasted.
Wade: Hold on, guys. Well, it got the rest of us a bunch of free liquor.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yep.
David Mendenhall: See what I do for my friends?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Wade: friends now.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
David Mendenhall: Saved your life a few times.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll kill them, and I think you actually killed them, too.
Wade: I, I…
David Mendenhall: I have no rough memory.
Wade: I thought… I did some damage, didn't I? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I think you accidentally killed Soma, if I recall correctly.
David Mendenhall: That's possible.
Wade: I thought it was the other way around, I thought I accidentally, like, earth-tremered on the party.
Wade: Or ice knife, or something like that.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, yeah.
David Mendenhall: It was the ice knife, yeah.
Wade: Yeah, I… I'm still figuring out how to be a Druid.
David Mendenhall: It's alright.
Wade: Yeah. Like, this Druid thing is new to me.
David Mendenhall: It's just how it goes.
Wade: I can turn into bear. I'm good at that.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, you are a good bear.
Wade: That was before I could transform.
Kostadis Roussos: Correct, so I need a name.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Isn't it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you arrive at the Falcon Lodge.
Kostadis Roussos: That you arrive for dinner.
Wade: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Dinner.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Wade: we've been at the Falcon Lunch.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, sorry, I meant, I meant the dinner part.
Kostadis Roussos: And there is, in fact, a drow a trowel.
Kostadis Roussos: And she sits… she sits down at…
Kostadis Roussos: Dinner with the rest of you.
Gary Young: Do I recognize her?
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to get a drought.
Gary Young: Well, I guess I would strike up a conversation. Have you come up here to enjoy the pain of the overbright?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see. Alright, let me put this straw here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, need to give her a name. I have the name, just give me one second.
Kostadis Roussos: And her name is… Sue Darth.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that's not the one.
Kostadis Roussos: Put the name down.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: she, she goes, oh, another… a fellow… a fellow under… a fellow resident of the Underdark. I noticed you're here.
Gary Young: Yes, but I've moved up here, where it is much, much more delightfully painful.
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses and looks at… she pauses and looks, and she goes, are you a cleric of Lathander?
Gary Young: Why, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You do understand the pain that light causes to drow, yes?
Gary Young: Yes.
Wade: Oh, does she ever.
David Mendenhall: Masochist.
Kostadis Roussos: Whoa!
Wade: Eww.
Kostadis Roussos: but she whispers, you're really a cleric of bluff, right?
Gary Young: No, no, no.
Gary Young: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Joe?
Kostadis Roussos: This is not some elaborate ruse.
Gary Young: Not this time.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so she… she…
Gary Young: What brings you up here?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I've become quite a collector of sorts.
Gary Young: And what are you collecting?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I've heard rumors of… Planar disruptions in the area.
Gary Young: Oh, yes. We know about this.
Kostadis Roussos: And I was wondering, and I've been looking for any kind of little curio you might have found, something that's not quite right. I've become very interested in those things.
Gary Young: Do we have something like that?
Wade: God, yeah, didn't we pick something up, or… Yeah, you did pick something up.
David Mendenhall: We sold all that stuff.
Wade: Did we?
Wade: It wasn't… no, the Black Pearl was from the… the lighthouse.
David Mendenhall: We sold it all.
Gary Young: Talisman of Moscow.
Kostadis Roussos: Talisman.
Wade: Oh, plot items, I was… all over.
David Mendenhall: Palestine?
Wade: Talisman of Moscow, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: of Moscow.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so that would be… that would be definitely something that was very… Weird.
Wade: peculiar.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Gary Young: Do we think it's important to us? It says plot item, but do we care about it?
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, I'm willing to pay… she goes, she goes, I'm willing to pay good money for any such device or gadget you find. I think I've become quite the… what's the word she's looking for? Collector.
Gary Young: And what can you do with such a thing?
Kostadis Roussos: Does one need a reason to collect curious things?
Gary Young: I guess not.
Kostadis Roussos: But I, I, I…
David Mendenhall: I'm the naive one.
Wade: We'd like to know before we sell, how about that?
Kostadis Roussos: Well.
Gary Young: What… why is… why is… what is going on with these Plater incursions? Like, seems to have got all the druids up here, you know, pretty feisty.
Wade: About half of them.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, well, look, I really can't, I don't know. But ever since that, the incident involving the blink in the Underdark when the Pharisees went blink and the demons came in, I've become quite intrigued. That's what happened in the.
Gary Young: Yeah, the blank, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And she goes, after the blink, after the blink, I've become very interested in learning more about planar events and planar transformations, and…
Kostadis Roussos: And I thought it would be a wonderful thing for me to… to…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Natasha's, TPK, every time she walks in and announces TPK.
Gary Young: Wait.
Gary Young: Insider 17, did I gain anything from…
David Mendenhall: Not tonight.
Kostadis Roussos: No servico.
Kostadis Roussos: Inside 17.
Kostadis Roussos: She's genuinely interested in those things.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, she's like, it's like a genuine, real interest.
Gary Young: Well… Oh, wait, we need to know whether you're an interventionist.
Wade: I am not anymore.
Wade: Or, sorry.
Gary Young: Are you up here?
Wade: No, I'm not a naturalist anymore. I thought I was a naturalist until I saw what batshit insanity the naturalists were, and I think now I'd be qualified as an interventionist.
Kostadis Roussos: But the naturalists are on the batshit crazy side.
Wade: Yeah, yeah, I'm not batshit crazy. I want there to be a world tomorrow.
Gary Young: Do you aim to intervene in the, the planar effects?
Wade: I would like to stop planar incursions, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so, but, but, but Sirdar says, she looks at you, she goes, interventionists? What is this?
Wade: There's a schism going on in the Emerald Enclave, I guess. I don't know, I'm not really part of them, like…
Wade: I'm a late-stage, late-in-life druid, you know, like…
Kostadis Roussos: The falcon, the hunter, goes, yes, Adabra and her ilk are convinced that everything evil comes from anyone intervening and trying to protect the world, and so we should just let it all burn to the ground.
Wade: they're…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade: They're off their rockers.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they're off the rockers. Cyrdar goes, Oh, Falcon, yes, we were talking about that just the other day. I… thank you for reminding me, I'd forgotten about that. No, of course not, I have nothing to do with that, I'm just a collector. I don't… I am not a member of the Emerald Enclave, I… I'm just a collector, a person who finds things interesting, that kind of thing.
Gary Young: So, do we want to be interventionists in the planar things? Like, is that…
Wade: Soma does.
David Mendenhall: I think Bukradin is in favor of that.
Wade: Yeah, I don't think anybody in the party was particularly comfortable with the, you know, shit coming into the.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, just let it all go to hell.
Gary Young: It seems like a problem.
Gary Young: Yes, we should stop this.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, she goes… but Sergei says, I think you should stop it, but I am just collecting items. I say, look, do you have anything? Any information? Any stories you might tell me? I'm willing to pay for either.
Gary Young: Thank you.
Wade: Tell us.
Gary Young: Certainly tell you a story, yeah.
Wade: Yeah, I mean, you're actually the one that watched the little dude collecting shit at the end, right?
Gary Young: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gary Young: So…
Gary Young: overall perception to… to see how well I remember the… the… the circumstances of… of that, and then… Right.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean…
Gary Young: 23.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so yeah.
Gary Young: I remember quite a bit of detail.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, she, Serdar goes, hmm, this is very interesting. I've never heard of such creatures and such events. And is this place still there?
Gary Young: Yes.
Wade: Didn't it all swallow up?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, it's… well, you guys left.
Wade: Oh, yeah, okay.
Gary Young: We left. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: We're able to stop the virtual thing, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No, you weren't.
Wade: too, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And she goes, well, well, well, this is very, very important. But for this kind of information, if you ever were to find it, I would gladly give you gold. Would 20 gold be enough?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And wine.
David Mendenhall: Did I want… you should go get me from outside.
David Mendenhall: Let me persuade her.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Nothing's gonna demand an apology.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Will there be refreshments as part of the reworld as well?
Kostadis Roussos: So you show up here, right, and he demands an apology.
David Mendenhall: What does he want me to apologize for?
Wade: Well, for calling him a crook…
Kostadis Roussos: Calling him a common thief.
Gary Young: Yup.
David Mendenhall: I'm sorry, you're a good host.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and you… and you roll a 15%.
David Mendenhall: I know, I gotta roll Deception.
Kostadis Roussos: 14.
Kostadis Roussos: But don't you have a silver tongue on deception?
David Mendenhall: With the 4… yeah, minimum 10! Minimum 10, and then I get the plus 4, 14, yes, that's how it works.
David Mendenhall: The Falcon is very… I get minimum 14 deception, minimum 15 persuasion.
Kostadis Roussos: He's… he… he buys it.
Gary Young: Bison.
David Mendenhall: Silver tongue.
Gary Young: So…
David Mendenhall: Now I gotta… now I gotta persuade, the drow to give us more money.
David Mendenhall: 21.
Gary Young: But I'd really rather have him tell us, like, more about, like, the plating recursions.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, that too.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I wanna know. Don't forget about the wine.
Wade: We love Brewberry.
David Mendenhall: I'm gonna ask you to ask for wine?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Refreshments. Anything else?
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Corwin shows up with more wine.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Excellent.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Excellent.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so just… Corman shows up with, more wine. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, the Falcon Hunter, so Sridhar, so what did you ask? I'm sorry, so Sridhar, looks at you and says, well.
Kostadis Roussos: you know, 20 gold pieces was a ridiculous amount of money. 30 gold pieces.
Kostadis Roussos: That's what she's getting.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's a 50% increase, not too bad.
Kostadis Roussos: And she goes, but if you have any artifacts, information is valuable, but the artifacts would be extremely valuable.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Define equals…
David Mendenhall: Tell her the talisman. Well, show her the talisman.
Wade: And I don't want to agree to sell it yet, I want to know, like, if there's anything valuable about it. Like, obviously, if she's gonna pay for it, it's gotta have some more. Show her the talisman.
Gary Young: Let her study it.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, she goes, oh, yes, yes, yes, this is definitely…
Kostadis Roussos: There's definitely a plainer connection with this thing. Absolutely, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. She goes, I'll buy it from you.
Wade: Wow.
Wade: Tell us more about it first.
Gary Young: I don't know if we're selling, but we'd be happy to let you study it.
Gary Young: 4 feet.
Gary Young: No.
Kostadis Roussos: I've had.
David Mendenhall: Out now?
David Mendenhall: thinking. Nice.
Kostadis Roussos: Here it is.
David Mendenhall: It's fair trade gold. We rarely get an opportunity to get real money. Let's do it.
Gary Young: That's why I'm reading it.
David Mendenhall: Look at this talisman, it's just sitting around in our backpack. We forgot we even had it.
Wade: I'm more worried what she's going to do with it, you know? Maybe she's gonna go make her own little.
Gary Young: She's just a drow. I mean, drow, we're all fine, right?
Wade: Oh, yes, you know, nothing's more trustworthy than a Dorao, thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, are you saying that you have issues with…
David Mendenhall: I would say Vukraddin knows Velfina. Velfina seems at least neutral, so he's not inclined to think that this drow is inherently evil.
Wade: I mean, we've heard the stories.
Kostadis Roussos: God, if you have.
David Mendenhall: No, I think the crowd hasn't heard the story.
Wade: Bukraden's young and dumb, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Credit and heard the story.
David Mendenhall: He's pro sell it and get the money, because it's fair trade gold.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so she takes it and says, well, she pauses and says, I don't know very much about this, but there has been…
Kostadis Roussos: And there have been many of these items that have been Well, the story's on.
Gary Young: That…
Kostadis Roussos: There have been all sorts of…
Kostadis Roussos: Trinkets that are imbued with planar energies that have appeared in the area.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why?
Kostadis Roussos: If I knew why, I would tell you. I'm just telling you the information I have.
Gary Young: So what are you doing? You're up here exploring, and research.
Kostadis Roussos: But ever since… she goes, ever since I… ever since the blink and the demons appeared.
Kostadis Roussos: the nature of interplaying their existence has fascinated me. I, you know, in fact, that is why the Falcon and I chatted about the interventionists and the naturalists. The naturalists were of the opinion that it was up to the naturalists, the demon lords underground would have turned the entire planet apart.
Kostadis Roussos: Whereas the interventionists would have saved them, and I'm absolutely an interventionist, especially after what happened in Melzo-Baranzen.
Gary Young: Oh, did you live there too?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, no, but I heard about it. Oh, okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So you don't know why it's happening, but what's your theory?
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, it could be anything. It could be magic users, it could be… it could be extraplanar entities, it could be fools meddling with things they don't understand, it could be all sorts of things. What exactly it is, I don't know. That's actually a very good question.
Gary Young: Maybe you'd like to help us figure this out.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, she goes, I would be delighted to help you figure this out. If you ever find any more information, just come to me, and I'd be more than delighted to see whether I could piece a few clues together.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Do you have any leads for us?
Kostadis Roussos: I've never really thought about.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: mission.
Kostadis Roussos: she goes, I've never really thought of it as actually being intentional, but, you know, now that you ask it, there might be some…
Kostadis Roussos: Thing going on here.
Kostadis Roussos: I just thought this was a natural phenomenon. And she goes, after all, as you… as Valfine knows, in the Underdark, we have the Farazes, which is an extra-planal ward, and not from the Overbright, of course, I lived in the Underdark for years, and when I came up here, I heard about these artifacts, and I thought this was just another example of…
Kostadis Roussos: How the world works.
Gary Young: Yes. That makes sense to me. I mean, the world is a hostile and dangerous place that's trying to kill you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Yes, exactly.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, think about it, you people walk out in the sun all day.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Like…
Gary Young: It's a dangerous, hostile environment.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? It burns, it's hot, it makes you sweat.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, I'm not the brightest barbarian, but all those events happening within the same area, how likely is it that it's a coincidence?
David Mendenhall: Sounds.
David Mendenhall: How much were we gonna get for the, talisman?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: She hasn't quoted yet.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I find Vukretin very greedy for a harnessed bard.
Wade: I did not see a lot of income.
Kostadis Roussos: He says, wow, she says, well, a hundred gold pieces? Would that be…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: and wine.
Kostadis Roussos: She turns to the falcon, and give this man 3 bottles of wine.
David Mendenhall: 150?
Kostadis Roussos: He just paid 30 gold pieces to get the wine for breweries.
David Mendenhall: That was nice of her, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And no, no, no, so that, she's got 20…
David Mendenhall: Councilman?
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's 120, because the 30 went to… she doesn't have any more money, dude.
David Mendenhall: Oh, okay, 120 plus the 30 for the information, so $150 total for the.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade: I just wanna know what she's gonna do with it.
Wade: That's a lot of money for something that she's just collecting.
David Mendenhall: Soma.
David Mendenhall: The thing about the rich is…
David Mendenhall: Buddy doesn't have the same sort of gain as them, you know?
David Mendenhall: They… They start to lose joy from everyday activities. They need to look for new ways to, like, get…
David Mendenhall: Vibrancy out of life, and…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Spending their money is how they do it, and they'll buy all sorts of things. It's just how it goes. I thought you were broke, so how would you know?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're creating.
David Mendenhall: 21 Persuasion on, on, Salsa.
Wade: Soma, yeah, I'll eat it. I'll eat, I'll eat it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade: Let her, let her buy it, that's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: So just for the record, Stefan, we said that he can roll persuasion, but characters, players…
David Mendenhall: No, I know, it doesn't actually have an effect. It's just…
Wade: No, I'll eat it, though, it's fine. No, no, no, and so players can choose to eat it, I'm just saying… Yes, yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Fair enough. Fair enough. So, yeah, just to be clear. So yes, he can roll, and you can say, yes.
David Mendenhall: I just want to point out, it's a very persuasive speech that I gave.
Kostadis Roussos: Someone responds to it is up to her. Yes. All right.
Wade: I'll… I'm fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so after dinner, the Falcon, the Hunter…
David Mendenhall: A 150… okay, I'm gonna record it.
Wade: Yep. You darn well got her, that's a lot of gold for this.
David Mendenhall: You already did, okay.
Gary Young: Hi, and is, is this, is this person a,
Gary Young: A spellcaster, a wizard? Or, just… Doesn't… they don't know.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Could I ask?
Wade: Hmm, burden.
Gary Young: Maybe…
David Mendenhall: adventurer?
Kostadis Roussos: Adventurer? No, I'm no adventurer. I'm… I'm just a traveler, a refugee.
David Mendenhall: How do you stay safe?
Kostadis Roussos: Coming so far from home, do you have a bodyguard?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the Falcon Hunter watched me…
David Mendenhall: I'm not talking to Falcon, I'm talking to the driver.
Kostadis Roussos: as she's explaining, Falcon the Hunter, she paid for him to bring her here.
David Mendenhall: Oh… Oh, you're with him. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: She's…
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade: Boy, that is.
Kostadis Roussos: What, what, what, why? No, no, not…
David Mendenhall: Oh, I've got nothing. I've got nothing to say.
Kostadis Roussos: Not in that way.
David Mendenhall: I'm good.
Kostadis Roussos: She's very confused right now.
Wade: Why is she…
David Mendenhall: Two guests in his home.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, yes. All right. Okay. After a wonderful dinner.
Gary Young: Did she hear my death chant earlier?
David Mendenhall: Yes, and it bombed.
Gary Young: And it bumped.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Okay. That's why she asked, are you really a cleric of Loth?
Gary Young: I see, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: It didn't sound like Lathandry music, it sounded more like… Wolf clerical chance.
David Mendenhall: Lot of clicking sounds.
David Mendenhall: There's a lot of clicking.
Kostadis Roussos: Illusion… there was a lot of 8-note beats.
David Mendenhall: Well done.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, all right, so he does say, but, you know, he says, well, there is a bit of a… there's a bit of a challenge I have, because… so he does give you an additional quest you can choose to explore, so I'm.
David Mendenhall: The, half works?
Kostadis Roussos: The Mets, yes.
David Mendenhall: Say again?
Kostadis Roussos: Got the woodland mats. Just put that.
David Mendenhall: Is that the half works?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Gary Young: Woodland Ants? Mance, Mance, let me… M-A-N-S-C…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, hold on.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What does he want us to do exactly? Investigate? The preemptive?
Gary Young: It's crazy.
David Mendenhall: Well…
Gary Young: Those tapes.
David Mendenhall: Forgs have stolen a lot of things.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, hold on, let me just… let me… let me answer. So, he goes…
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, right now, they don't seem to be causing any problems, so he goes, I don't really have anything to say.
Gary Young: You know, if you ever decide to go…
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he looks at you and says, he says, well…
Kostadis Roussos: I could have a quest for you, but I think you're… I think you need to get a little bit more experience before you're ready to handle it.
David Mendenhall: Other than the half-orcs?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Alright, before we break, I'd like to… since you'll have to figure this one out, Castadas…
David Mendenhall: While everyone is sleeping, I would like to stealthily search… for… the Dragon Horde.
David Mendenhall: So that I can get information on it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Gary Young: You're not gonna steal it from…
David Mendenhall: I think I won't steal it. I think… I think what I want to do is…
David Mendenhall: Get information and go get the rightful owner of that stuff to come here to try to make
David Mendenhall: Our hunter friend understand what he has done.
Wade: Hmm.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: In keeping this stuff from whose it is, rightfully.
Wade: It was the dragon that stole it all originally, but yeah.
David Mendenhall: Well, yeah.
David Mendenhall: But…
Kostadis Roussos: Our friend Horde kept the horde instead of returning it. Yeah, so you said, who does the horde belong to, right? Does it belong to the… dragons are very possessive about their hordes.
David Mendenhall: Yeah. Well, the dragon is dead.
Gary Young: Who does number 2 work for?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, now the horde, or a quarter of the horde, belongs to our friend the Hunter.
David Mendenhall: But let's see if we can figure out who the original owner was.
Wade: That'll be hard.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, somehow.
Wade: We don't actually have any sort of provenance magic, right? Like…
David Mendenhall: I think I have, like, Identify or stuff like that, but…
Wade: Does that actually reveal that kind of thing?
David Mendenhall: What did we need? We needed legend Lore, is that what we determined?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Gary Young: I believe I had Locate Object, but I don't think that helped.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Wade: I mean, it would help you find, like, the other half of a BFF necklace or something.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he does say, when you, when you, he got, he does say… Alright.
David Mendenhall: So he does actually talk to them.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, I'm just gonna say, he does offer… he says, if you do ever, by the way, deal with the half-orcs and the woodland mans, there's a boot… there's a pair of boots of elvenkind for you.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: You're gonna give… you have Boots of Elvenkind, which you're gonna give to us?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, what size? I have big feet.
David Mendenhall: size.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the good news is these boots can fit at any…
Wade: One size fits all?
Kostadis Roussos: They, they are, they are food, they are… they adjust their size. He does make a point, though. He says, he looks at, he looks, he goes, he looks at… don't worry, I purchased those boots.
David Mendenhall: With… I'm gonna hold my tongue.
Kostadis Roussos: With the proceeds, the only part.
Wade: It's all in gold.
Kostadis Roussos: What's the proceeds of this establishment.
Gary Young: Establishment built on stolen gold, yes.
David Mendenhall: Soma is finally starting to understand.
Wade: Oh, that's Wade, Soma doesn't say that.
Kostadis Roussos: He's just trying really hard to tell you that this is the.
David Mendenhall: I'm just… Shitting there. I'm not gonna say anything.
Kostadis Roussos: And you're, you're, you're, you're… he's…
David Mendenhall: Generous of you to share your home with us.
Kostadis Roussos: There he goes.
Wade: Edge or wine.
Kostadis Roussos: And your wine. Alright, okay, so Tuesday… Are folks free next Friday?
Wade: Boom!
Gary Young: I'll be back in town.
David Mendenhall: Right now, Thursday would be better.
Kostadis Roussos: What's Thursday?
Wade: Can I do…
Gary Young: Thursday will be… I, you know, like, again, it'll be in York, it'll be midnight.
David Mendenhall: flying out Friday morning. New York next week, too?
Gary Young: I will be back Friday evening, California time.
David Mendenhall: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's do Friday.
Wade: David couldn't do that.
David Mendenhall: I think I'll, probably pass then.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the reason I'm saying that is.
Gary Young: Or you can go without me.
Gary Young: On Thursday, or Tuesday.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, we… We could go without you on Thursday?
Gary Young: Or Tuesday.
Kostadis Roussos: On Tuesday?
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: I can't do Tuesday.
Kostadis Roussos: So let's do Thursday. And if, Gary, you decide to join us, you decide to join us.
Gary Young: Okay, it will be midnight, and I will be getting up 4 hours later for.
David Mendenhall: It'll be midnight for me, too, if that makes you feel better, and I'll also… I have a…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Exactly, what's 4 hours less or more, you know?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, we're doing the same thing, Gary.
Wade: You can sleep on the plane.
Gary Young: Okay, well…
David Mendenhall: It's up to.
Kostadis Roussos: So, here's the deal.
Gary Young: We'll see.
Kostadis Roussos: We'll try… we're saying for Thursday, if it works out, it works out. We'll see, yeah. If it works out, it works out. Just so you know, the week after… the reason I said we should try to meet next week is because the week after, I'm going to be in India, and then the week after that, I'm going to be in Belgium.
Kostadis Roussos: The India might be a little bit tricky, because there's, like, all-day off-sites, but in Belgium, I'll find out…
David Mendenhall: Where are you in India?
Kostadis Roussos: Bangalore.
David Mendenhall: Oh, me too.
Gary Young: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: You gonna be in Bangalore next week?
David Mendenhall: No, the same week you're gonna be there.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, we should, like, meet up and, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Stare at you. Yeah, stare at each other.
David Mendenhall: Although I hear, like, it really depends where you are in Bangalore, because it's, like, 3 hours from one side of the city to the.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't know, one side of the city, it's 3 blocks. Going 3 blocks takes 3.
David Mendenhall: Alright, bye guys.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, bye. Bye, guys.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, thank you.